[{"answer": "Mr. Vice President, I know --", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "He sent me two letters saying by the way, can you send me some stimulus money?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the buck has to stop somewhere.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "How plausible is that?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "That part is hard to say.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Look, my dad's a wonderful, wonderful father.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "So, my immediate question to you is, does your dad do that scary laugh to his own kids?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "EAU BIDEN: Well, look, you know, I thought he did what we set out to do and that's communicate directly to the American people what he and the president want to continue doing for the middle class.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Did you feel in the moment that your dad had won quite easily?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Does he feel that?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Look, the military does what it's asked to do.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "If the Republicans were to win and actually put more troops in Afghanistan, what would that do, do you think, to the morale of the military?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I sure do.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "You know what the unemployment rate in Scranton is today?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Oh, that's a very good question.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "If you're the guy who's being Paul Ryan for days on end, how do you feel watching the real thing happening without you?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Well, it's hard to know how to read these polls.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Why did not more people think that your man won?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't do that.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "When you were being Paul Ryan, were you nervously gulping water every three minutes in the prep?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, look, I'm not trying to go for any Academy Awards on the acting side.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Do you actually put on a Paul Ryan voice when you're pretending to be him?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "I think Joe Biden won the debate.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "But what -- who do you think won last night?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "No, I don't agree with that, but I think it is possible for Republicans to really think their guy won and for Democrats to really think their guy won.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Kristen, do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I think staying hydrated is really important.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Kristen Soltis, what did you make of his extraordinary water intake because Joe Biden didn't drink at all?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, I think Joe Biden clearly had a lot of Mountain Dew before he went on the debate, where Paul Ryan favored the water.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Carol Roth, would you rather have a presidential, vice presidential candidate who drinks a lot of water in a nervous way or one like Joe Biden who toughs it out?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Look, I don't think how much Joe Biden smiled or how hydrated Paul Ryan is, is going to decide the election, but I agree with you.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "As it went on, I found it increasingly infectious and began laughing with him, which can't help Ryan, can it?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Sure he did.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "You did ask for stimulus money?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "No, he shouldn't be grateful about the stimulus.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "So he should be grateful, really, to the government for providing it, right?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well, it depends on who you're voting for.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "It's very, very important that Barack Obama comes back with a win, isn't it?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "No, no, I don't think so.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Don't you?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Look what's happened since.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "If he lost by the same degree that he lost the other night, wouldn't that really be the end?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I think you are going to see another really great performance from Governor Romney.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Kristen, last word to you, how do you think it will go on Tuesday?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yes, and I had to go feel really uncomfortable until I had a good night.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I think I'm there.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Can you be as good sober?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "We played in Chicago back then, the Eagles did, and we had a -- we were on top of the world and we had a great show.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "I could give you five hours to relive the party, what would you go for?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Belushi was the top dog, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "I'm historically a Democrat, but I don't agree with either of them 100 percent.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "How are you seeing it this time around?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Congress is the problem.", "docId": "121012pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Who will it be or haven't you decided yet?", "qSentId": 550}]